{
    "subject": "resource/Caract\u00e8res",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/depiction",
    "object": "http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Special:FilePath/Caracteres.svg",
    "human_readable": "The depiction of Caract\u00e8res is http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Special:FilePath/Caracteres.svg.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7950022220611572,
            "question": "Which website hosts the depiction of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7883787155151367,
            "question": "Where can you find the depiction of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7814986705780029,
            "question": "What is the format of the depiction of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7574822306632996,
            "question": "Can you describe the content of the depiction of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7437615394592285,
            "question": "Is there any text associated with the depiction of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7290626764297485,
            "question": "What type of file is 'Caracteres.svg'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6719647645950317,
            "question": "What information can you gather about 'Caracteres' from its depiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6606762409210205,
            "question": "What is depicted in 'Caracteres.svg'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6054663062095642,
            "question": "What platform or system is used to access the depiction of Caract\u00e8res?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5517324805259705,
            "question": "Is the depiction of Caract\u00e8res a physical object or a digital image?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The depiction of Caract\u00e8res is http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Special:FilePath/Caracteres.svg.",
            "html": "dbpedia_109_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What platform or system is used to access the depiction of Caract\u00e8res?",
            "html": "dbpedia_109_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is depicted in 'Caracteres.svg'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_109_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What information can you gather about 'Caracteres' from its depiction?",
            "html": "dbpedia_109_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_109_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "I cannot provide information about depictions of specific books based on the given context. \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "**Repeat**\nNo approximatedepiction,you can judge [...]\nat once on the quality ground of your pictures without waiting to view them on your computer.\nPas de rendu approximatif, vous pourrez [...]\njuger imm\u00e9diatement sur le terrain de la qualit\u00e9 de vos clich\u00e9s sans attendre de\n\n[...]\n\nles visionner sur votre ordinateur."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Query: The depiction of characters (glyphs or font) is located at http://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Special:FilePath/Caracteres.svg.\n   Response: {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "The depiction of Caract\u00e8res is a visual representation used for the display of character data, often in the form of glyphs or fonts."
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided context focuses on various aspects of depiction, such as visual representations in art and literature, character portrayals, and the use of language to describe something. It doesn't mention or relate to online image files or specific URLs like Wikipedia.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided does not contain any mention of a file path or an image on Wikimedia Commons related to \"Caract\u00e8res\", which makes the statement unrelated to the given context.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}